（忆往昔）
猜怎么着 克劳力叔叔 我饿了
Guess what, uncle Crowley? I'm hungry.
阿玛拉在像草一样疯长吗
So, Amara's growing like a radioactive weed?
她在大吃灵魂
By stuffing her face with souls.
如果她的法力有我想的一半的强
If she's half as powerful as I think she is,
我一定要她站在我这边
I want her on my team.
黑暗有无限的力量
The Darkness is almost infinite power.
我们是联系在一起的 迪恩
We're bound, Dean.
上帝以前收拾过这东西一次
God kicked this thing's ass once before.
我们需要帮助 上帝
we need your help, God.
但你们都清楚
You know who we need.
我们需要谁来帮忙应付黑暗
to help deal with the Darkness.
找到你了 恶魔石碑
Hello, demon tablet.
他是上帝的书记官 他什么事都听到了
He was God's scribe. He did hear about everything.
马德森警探
Detective Madsen?
- 我之前看到附近有个人 - 那是伦
- I saw a guy hanging around earlier. - That's Len.
我觉得阿玛拉吸食了他的灵魂
I think Amara sucked out his soul.
我会担下所有的凶案
I'll confess to all the murders.
天哪
Holy crap.
那样我就出不来了
That way, I can't get out.
我们不能杀他 他还没干过坏事呢
We can't kill him 'cause he hasn't done anything yet.
迪恩 我们也不想杀他啊
Dean, we don't…want to kill him.
我们是想救人的 记得吗
We want to save people, remember?
是啊 你的新规矩
Right, your new rules.
- 我能帮什么忙 - 不不
- What can I do to help? - No, no, no,
你坐好 休息一下
You just, uh, sit there and take a breather,
- 看看网飞什么的 - 好吧
- watch some Netflix. - Okay.
另外 我们还有更要紧的事要操心
Besides, we got bigger fish to fry.
再见 迪恩 回头见了
Bye, Dean. I'll see you soon.
（如今）
她说约会会让我无心顾及学业
So, she says dating's gonna break my focus for academics,
但我暑假时可以约会
but that I'm allowed to date over summer break.
那要怎么做啊
How does that work? Like…
你好 我是歌蒂
Hi, I'm Goldie,
我只在六月到八月间可以恋爱
I'm only romantically available from June to August,
想跟我稳定下来吗
but want to go steady?"
我恨她 看我啊
I hate her. Like, look at me.
我还得跑来铁路边吃小零食
I have to hang out by the tracks just to get my snack on.
她不许你吃薯片吗
She won't let you eat chips?
允许是允许
She'll let me, but…
但她也是为了能一直摆出这副表情
but just so she can make this face the whole time.
「抱歉了 老妈
It's like, "Sorry, mom.
我不能像你那样光吃薄荷糖和无糖汽水「
I can't survive on menthol and diet soda like you can."
什么 不行
What? No.
我也恨我爸妈 歌蒂 他们最烦了
Look, I hate my parents, too, Goldie. They suck.
但我得遵守宵禁
But I got a curfew.
再见
Bye.
好吧
Fine.
再见
Bye.
你父母呢
Where are your parents?
我没有父母
I don't have any parents.
真遗憾
Sorry.
你没事吧 你需要什么吗
Are you okay? Do you want something?
我想像你一样
I want to be like you.
半夜去吃宵夜了
Midnight snack?
别以为我不知道你最近在做什么
Don't think I don't know what you've been up to.
你可以否认 但证据…
You can try to deny it, but the evidence is…
确凿
well.
你叫我别再吃你的恶魔的
You told me to stop feeding on your demons.
我这不就不吃了吗
Well… I stopped feeding on demons.
我不是说得很清楚吗
I thought I was clear.
你这样出去 被人看到
Going out there, where they can see you…
太冒险了
it's too risky.
我是个长身体的女孩
I'm a growing girl.
我需要吃东西
I need to eat.
在这里 行为是有后果的 阿玛拉
Actions have consequences around here, Amara.
你在宫里已经疯了一把
You've had the run of the court.
我们见识到你的作风了
We've seen what you've made of it.
相信我 这对我来说
Believe me, this is going to hurt me.
会更加痛苦
way more than it hurts you.
抱歉 亲爱的
I'm sorry, my dear.
你被禁足了
You're grounded.
你是很强大
You're strong.
但记住了 我更强大
But you need to remember… I'm stronger.
暂时而已
For now.
是啊
Yeah.
[邪恶力量 第11季第6集]
（马萨诸塞州 福尔河）
你还说觉得那个准没错呢
Said you had a good feeling about that one.
感觉是条好线索的 迪恩
Yeah, well, it seemed like a solid lead, Dean.
只有没魂的变态才会杀了家里的宠物猫
Only a soulless psycho would kill the family cat.
除非是宠物猫
Yeah, unless the family cat.
自己钻进烘干机里睡觉了
decides to take a nap in the dryer.
我们从周一就一直待在这里
You know, we've been here since Monday.
还是没找到别的受害者
and still haven't found another legit victim.
或许阿玛拉去别处 或干脆停止进食了
Maybe Amara moved on or stopped feeding altogether.
找到被她吸魂的人
Well… Finding her victims.
仍是找到她的最佳机会
is still the best shot we got at finding her.
并不是的
Not actually true.
怎么 你觉得他准备好了吗
Oh, what? You think he's ready?
他最近挺惨的
He's had a pretty rough go of it lately.
我们谁不是
Which one of us hasn't?
让我们唯一的天使朋友在家闲着太不合理了
Seems insane to leave our one and only angel friend on the bench.
我打给他
I'll call him.
谢谢
Thank you.
真的无所谓
…It literally doesn't matter.
我们稍后就公布所有结果
Well, we're gonna get to all the results in just a second.
我们首先说说…
We're gonna start with, uh…
回到我们的第一则报道吧
Let's go back to our first story.
路易斯 希拉和埃德温
Uh, Louis, Silla, and Edwin.
小卡 你还好吗 伙计
Cass. How you doing, buddy?
我们给路易斯做了DNA检测
We did a DNA test on Louis.
我挺好
Oh, I'm fine.
查到梅塔特隆的线索了吗
Find anything on Metatron?
天使无线电上没消息
Um, nothing on angel radio.
你多久没出过地堡了
How long's it been since you left the bunker?
我为什么要离开啊
Oh, why would I leave?
这里什么都有了
I've got everything I need right here.
等等 那是…
Wait. Is that…
你是在看《珍妮·琼斯秀》吗
Are you watching "Jenny Jones"?
是重播
It's a rerun.
她刚要宣布亲子鉴定结果了
She's just about to announce the paternity results.
你就是父亲
You are the father.
珍妮 他还没准备好做父亲呢
Jenny, he is not ready to be a father.
好吧 我以为你在连看
Okay. I-I-I thought you were going.
三观比较正的节目呢
with socially acceptable binge watching.
《火线》《权力的游戏》什么的
Uh, you know, "The wire, " "Game of thrones."
人不能只吃鱼子酱啊 迪恩
Yeah, well, a man can't live on caviar alone, Dean.
你听起来怪怪的
Well, you sound weird, okay?
不太好的那种怪
Bad weird.
我也经历过这种事
Now, I've been down this road before.
什么事 警探
What's up, detective?
我也听到过电视机里传出的海妖之歌
I have heard the siren's song from the idiot box,
告诉你 不管你想找什么
and I'm telling you, whatever you're looking for,
你是不会在那儿找到的
you won't find it in there.
帮个忙
So do me a favor.
把电视关了 出去透口气
Turn off the TV. Go outside and get some air.
我们这边什么情况都不知道
We're in the dark here, pal.
我需要你重回战场
I need you back in the game, okay?
我知道了
I get it.
多谢知会
Yeah, well, thanks for letting me know.
我们这就过去
We'll… we'll head out there right now.
好的
You got it.
- 怎么了 - 马德森警探来电
- What's up? - That was Detective Madsen.
记得我们那位朋友 伦吗
Remember our friend Len?
怪咖 没魂
Uh, weird as hell, soulless,
替罪羊伦吗
took-the-rap-for-all-the-murders Len?
嗯
Yeah.
他死了
He's dead.
小卡 小卡
Cass! Cass!
别这样
Don't do this.
这不是你 是咒语的影响
Okay, this isn't you. It's the spell.
你能克服的
You can beat this.
我灭了你
I will end you!
不要
No!
别
Don't!
我不会让你离开这里
I won't let you walk out of this room.
马可昨晚处理掉一个
Marco got one of them last night…
伦·弗莱彻
A Len Fletcher?
叫马可接着找
Tell Marco to keep looking.
我最不需要的就是阿玛拉留下的糖纸
The last thing I need is one of Amara's candy wrappers.
跟天使或猎人说
blabbing to angels or hunters about what,
他们遭遇了谁
who happened to them.
人都哪去了
Where is everyone?
我们人手最近有些不够
Oh, our ranks have been a bit thin.
因为都被阿玛拉吃了
since Amara ate everybody.
我准备了新数据 您上朝前可以看看
I've got some fresh numbers for you to go over before court.
灵魂预测 不太理想
Soul projections… they're not good.
这一季指标很低 所以…
We're down for the quarter, which means that…
那扇门应该全天候锁住守住的
That door was supposed to be locked and guarded 24/7.
当然 陛下
Of course, sir.
怎么没有守卫啊
I don't see a guard.
嗯 肯定是搞错了
Uh, right. Must be a mix-up.
我们缺人手嘛
We're short-staffed and all, so…
恭喜 你被降职了
Congratulations. You've been demoted.
不许任何人进出那个房间
No one goes in or out of that room.
（监禁区 闲人免进）
本以为是哪个伦杀害的人的亲属干的
Thought maybe a relative of one of Len's victims,
但又不像是报复杀人
but it doesn't feel like a revenge killing.
太干净了 简直像刺杀
Too clean, like an assassination.
- 警探 - 失陪
- Detective. - Excuse me.
- 闻到了 - 嗯
- You smell that? - Yeah.
要么那位警探需要改变饮食习惯 要么就是
Yeah, either the detective needs to change his diet or, uh…
硫磺 是恶魔杀了伦
Sulfur. Len was killed by a demon.
恶魔为什么要刺杀没魂的普通人啊
Yeah, but why would a demon order a hit on a guy with no soul?
空卖力没好处啊
It's like a Cracker Jack but not a prize.
别碰我 废物警官
Hands off, deputy doody!
那女孩是谁
Who's the girl?
歌蒂·施密特拉普
Goldie Schmidtlapp.
本来挺正常 今早发狂
Was a normal kid, snapped this morning…
企图用煎锅杀她妈妈
tried to kill her mom with a frying pan.
先是斧子杀人案 然后是伦 又出这事
First the ax murders, then Len, now this?
我们得跟她谈谈
We're gonna need to talk to the kid.
四条腿驾驭四个轮
That's four legs on four wheels.
当自己是人的狗狗啊
Ah, that dog thinks it's people.
接下来 奥马哈州一则令人心痛的报道
Up next, a very upsetting story out of Omaha.
昨晚 市区一场酒吧殴斗升级酿成惨剧
A downtown bar fight escalated tragically last night.
《OWW2新闻》
And "OWW2 News"
为您带来了事件的独家视频
brings you an exclusive video of the event.
即将播放的视频十分血腥
The footage you're about to view is extremely graphic.
（市区枪击案）
受害者抢救无效…
Efforts were made to resuscitate the victim, but unfor…
警官 我还没打上电话呢
Hey, officer. I still haven't gotten my phone call.
我能叫个匹萨送进来吗
Do you think I could get a pizza delivered in here?
你不是警官
You're not the deputy.
不是
Nope.
老大的女儿最近在镇上到处闯祸
Boss' daughter's been making a mess in town,
所以我得负责收拾残局
and it's my job to clean it up.
别往心里去
Nothing personal.
干得好 歌蒂
Nice work, Goldie.
克劳力和阿玛拉啊
So, Crowley and Amara?
起床啦 帅哥
Rise and shine, buttercup.
关于之前你说的话
Now…about what you were saying.
克劳力跟阿玛拉在一起做什么
What's Crowley doing with Amara?
不知道 不在乎
Don't know, don't care.
就是知道也不会说
Wouldn't tell you if I did.
我们已经知道她长得很快
Well, we already know she's growing up fast.
嗯 恶魔灵魂 对身体有好处
Yeah, well, demon souls… they do a body good.
那小东西把我半数的朋友都吃了
Little muppet tore through half my buds.
克劳力才开始让她节食
before Crowley put her on a diet.
她不怎么高兴
She didn't like that.
就开始偷溜出去找吃的
Started sneaking out to get her fill.
你们也知道孩子什么德行
You know how kids are.
但爸爸毫不讲情面
But daddy put his foot down.
他把她藏哪了
Where's he hiding her?
我乐意继续跟你们八卦
I'm happy to keep gossiping with you boys,
但你们想要有用情报
but you want actionable intelligence?
随你折磨我吧
Torture me if you want.
我知道你最后反正也会杀了我
I know you'll just kill me anyway.
看来是陷入僵持了
Well, it looks like a stalemate to me.
那我们这就杀了他吧
I guess we go ahead and kill him right now.
不不 迪恩 等等
No, no, no. Dean, wait.
我们可以给他驱魔
We can exorcise him.
什么
What?
救他的肉身
Save his meat suit.
依我看
My two cents?
你给我驱魔 让我变烟离开
You exorcise me, let me smoke on out of here,
我保证不会告诉克劳力
I give you my word not to tell Crowley.
你也听到了
Hey, you heard me.
他现在也不算是我最喜欢的人
He's hardly my favorite guy at the moment. I…
等等 闭嘴
Wait a second. Shut up.
看啊
Well, would you look at that.
这样的伤口 他的肉身肯定活不成了
There's no way his suit survived that wound.
那好吧
All right.
该死
Crap.
（下载定位数据）
（歌蒂/阿玛拉 莉兹·波顿宅 酒吧/希德妮）
尸体丢哪了
Where'd you ditch the body?
- 学校操场 - 别闹
- School playground. - Come on.
医院停车场 有什么发现
Hospital parking lot. What do you got?
好消息 我黑了他的手机
Well, uh, good news. I was able to hack his phone.
拿到了他呼叫记录的坐标
Got the coordinates of his call history.
克劳力肯定是派他去跟踪阿玛拉还是什么的
I guess Crowley must've had him tailing Amara or something,
他三个地方都去了
'cause he was at all three spots.
莉兹·波顿的房子
He was at the Lizzie Borden house,
伦是在那儿被吸了魂
where Len got his soul taken,
还去了希德妮被吸魂的酒吧
he was at the bar where Sydney got her soul taken,
还有这里
and he was here,
歌蒂说阿玛拉找上她的地方
where Goldie said Amara approached her.
- 那么是在这个区域里 - 嗯 可能吧
- So, somewhere in there. - Yeah, maybe.
我不懂的是
But what I don't get is,
克劳力为什么要把阿玛拉安置在地球上
why would Crowley have Amara on earth in the first place?
把她留在地狱里不是更明智吗
Wouldn't it be smarter to… to keep her in hell?
是啊 但那样他就得老在那儿待着了
Yeah, but then he'd have to spend more time there,
他讨厌那里
and he hates that place.
是啊
Oh, right.
我老是忘记你和克劳力的夏日恋情
I keep forgetting about you and Crowley's summer of love.
我看不出这范围内会有哪里他比较喜欢
I'm not seeing much inside this radius that he'd like better.
- 有农场 沼泽地 - 嗯
- I mean, you got farms, you got swamps. - Yeah.
这个POI什么意思
This P.O.I., what's that?
可能地点
Point of interest.
我知道是什么…那里是什么地方
I know what it… what is it?
- 查查看吧 - 嗯
- Let's find out. - Yeah.
（尼达姆疯人院 1963年废弃）
（本地疯人院关闭）
是尼达姆疯人院
The Needham Asylum.
63年废弃了
Decommissioned in '63.
你觉得像克劳力会喜欢的地方吗
Sound like Crowley's kind of place to you?
看什么呢
What are you looking at?
还在努力了解世界的一切吗
Still learning all you can about the world?
如果无厘头标语
If nonsensical slogans.
搭配傻逼宠物图片
attached to idiotic pictures of domestic animals.
也算世界的话
counts as the world.
什么
Excuse me?
米姆
Memes.
我知道你觉得我的规矩
Look, I know to you my rules seem…
不公平 很武断
unfair, arbitrary,
好像我是有意想伤害你
as though I'm doing all this just to hurt you.
我才不管你为什么做你做的事
I don't care why you do anything.
我只希望你明白 我没那么坏
I just want you to know that I'm not a monster.
基维斯
Jervis?
你不能随心所欲地吃
I can't have you eating whatever, whenever,
不分时间 食物和多少
however much you want.
我想你或许想来点点心
I thought you might appreciate a little snack.
我不饿
I'm not hungry.
你继续看米姆吧
I'll leave you to your memes.
我心里真是一点底没有
I have no idea what I'm doing here…
什么都不知道
not a bleeding clue.
每时每刻 怎么能逗你开心
Moment to moment, what makes you happy?
什么会惹到你
What will set you off?
我怎么跟你建立感情
How do I even begin to forge a connection with you?
但我知道 你长得飞快
But what I do know is you're growing so fast,
这让我害怕
and it terrifies me.
当然了
I bet.
你留着我 不过是为了我将来能拥有的力量
You only want me for the power I'll wield,
而且你知道 我很快就不需要你了
and you know, soon enough, I won't need you anymore.
我们真要这么做吗
So, we're really gonna do this…
- 现在就去 - 当然了
- Now? - Hell, yeah.
自锡达拉皮兹市的事之后
I've been looking for a chance to get back at Crowley.
我就一直想找机会报复克劳力
ever since that crap he pulled in Cedar Rapids,
尤其现在我得知他骗了我
especially now that I know he tricked me.
跟黑暗一起跑了
and made off with the Darkness.
不 我不是那个意思
No, that's not what I meant.
我们要去杀阿玛拉
We're going in to kill Amara.
你准备好了吗
Are you ready for that?
我为什么会没准备好
Why wouldn't I be?
因为 我们对她毫不了解 迪恩
Because we don't know the first thing about her, Dean.
我们不了解她有什么本事
We don't know her powers.
我们不知道怎么除掉她
We don't know how to take her down.
我们都不知道她是不是能被杀死
Hell, you know what? We don't even know if she can be killed.
我知道
I know.
但她是个太大的威胁 不能再拖了
But she's too big of a threat to wait.
要我说 我们冲进去
I say we go in there.
使尽全力攻击她
and we hit her with everything we got.
你有很强大的力量
You have tremendous power,
很快你会拥有更大力量
and soon you'll have even more.
但我也有你缺的东西
But I have something you lack…
智慧 经验
Wisdom, experience.
我曾帮忙把路西法关进牢笼
I helped put Lucifer back in his cage.
我在地狱一步步爬上来
I rose through the ranks of hell,
击败一切对手 取得了王冠
defeated all comers, to claim the throne.
尽管曾遭遇几次挫折
And, a few minor setbacks aside,
我还稳坐王位
I'm still here.
我不知道该如何向你传授我所学
I don't know how to impart what I've learned to you,
该怎么教你
how to teach you.
凭你长大这速度
And at the rate that you're growing,
我恐怕永远没机会想明白了
I'll probably never get the chance to figure it out.
或许你不需要我教
Perhaps you don't need my tutelage.
但我深信
But I believe, deep down in my gut,
我是有东西可以给你的
I have something to offer you.
如果你肯给我个机会的话
If you'd just give me the chance.
你想要什么
What are you asking for?
时间
Time.
慢下来
Slow down.
再按我的规矩多坚持一会儿
Play by my rules for just a little bit longer.
你给我耐心
You give me your patience,
我会给你保护
I'll give you my protection…
直到你认为你再不需要我的保护了
…Until you decide you don't need it anymore.
好吧
Okay.
这个不错
Oh, this is good.
绝佳的头条啊
A night-leader if ever I saw one.
至少能挣五百
And this is gonna fetch me $500, minimum.
我知道
I, uh… I know that.
五百听起来不少
$500 sounds like plenty,
但考虑到我的开支
but with my overhead…
爸爸也得吃饭啊
…Daddy's got to eat.
拜托
Oh, come on!
救命 求你
Help. Please.
抱歉 伙计 你活了 就不是新闻了
I'm sorry, buddy. Y-you live, there's no story.
曾几何时
You know, there was a time.
我只需要一个弹指
I could have brought you back from the brink.
就能救你一命
with a snap of my fingers…
虽然我未必会那么做
Not that I would have.
但我不比从前了
But I'm not that guy anymore.
我救不了你
I can't save you.
我能
I can.
你怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
跟你找到他的办法一样
Same way you found him.
听警用频道
Scoured the police scanners,
赶在警察前出现
got ahead of the authorities.
那是什么
What was that?
怎么了
What?
实拍天使
Look, a real-life angel caught on tape?
比随机杀人事件精彩多了
That is way better than some random homicide.
你知道
Do you have any idea.
我偷了多少东西然后当掉换钱
how much stuff I had to steal and then pawn.
才买来那个吗
to pay for that?!
没人守卫吗
No guards at the perimeter?
看来门口也没有守卫
Looks like there are no guards at the door, either.
你还觉得我们没找错吗
You think this is the right place still?
有守护魔符
Well…Warding sigils.
给人类准备了这个
And for the humans… look at this.
中学储物柜用的挂锁
A padlock you'd find on a middle-school locker.
自大的混蛋
Cocky son of a bitch.
迪恩 外围安保可能比较松懈
Dean, external security may be lax,
但我们不知道在里面会遇到多少恶魔
but we still don't know how many demons we're gonna face inside.
那就进去看看
Well, let's find out.
翻到27页的图谱
Turn to the graph at the bottom of 27,
可以看到这三年来
and you'll see a nearly 40% decrease.
太平洋西北地区灵魂收集
in soul collections in the Pacific Northwest.
减少近40%
over the past three years.
或许是大麻合法化的意外结果
An unexpected consequence of legalized marijuana?
有些分析家是这样认为
Some analysts think so.
也有人不敢确定
Others are not quite so sure.
（她为什么对着干 理解你叛逆的青春期女儿）
好吧 马文
Okay, "Marv"…
你偷兜
You're picking pockets,
见死不救
leaving a man to die.
真不知我以为会是怎么样
I-I… I don't know what I expected,
但这太让人失望了
but this is disappointing.
你还好意思说
One to talk.
你选择了工资奴隶的生活
You chose the life of a wage slave,
打工赚钱 过了多久
slinging slurpees for, what, a month?
我可是要活出精彩来
I am in it to win it.
你夺走我能量后 我可什么都没有
I was at zero when you took my grace,
躲避天使 一文不名
Hiding from angels, not a cent to my name.
但我找到了自己的天职
But I found my calling,
我自力更生 改变人生
and I pulled myself up by my bootstraps.
建立了一份生意
and started a business.
而且我的故事才刚刚开始
And, you know, my story has only just begun.
什么故事
What story is that?
你像个秃鹫一样以他人的惨剧为食
You're preying like a vulture on human tragedy.
卡西迪奥
Castiel!
你还活在哪个世纪啊
What century are you in?
宗教已经死了
Religion is dead!
小说 死得更透
The novel? Deader.
你以为我耻于
You think I'm ashamed.
靠转瞬而逝的视觉冲击挣钱吗
for dealing in fleeting visual sensation,
或是恐怖 颓废 堕落的惊鸿一瞥
in gift-length glimpses of horror, waste, and degradation?!
才不
No!
我只是跟上时代
I just caught up with the times.
现实是我们这个时代的伟大文学
Reality is the great literature of our era,
我每晚都会去街上
and I am out there, on the streets,
捕捉现实
every single night, capturing it!
我就是现实的作者
I am reality's author.
省省你的故事吧 我不是为那个而来
Oh, save your story. It is not what I came for.
那就直接谈正事喽
So… straight to business.
你想要恶魔石碑
You want the demon tablet?
你是找不到的
Well, you're not gonna get it.
我十分小心地把它藏在
I have hidden it very carefully.
一个你和你的朋友们…
in a place where you and your friends …
你把石碑藏在你的床垫下面
You hid it under your mattress.
电视台把你的地址给了我
The TV station gave me your address,
我把你那里搜了一遍
and I-I checked the place out.
你知道你家有臭虫吧
You realize you have bedbugs?
你居然擅闯我的公寓
You broke into my apartment?
你对黑暗有什么了解
What do you know about the Darkness?
是乐队吗
The band?
好啦
Okay.
有时 深夜写东西时
Sometimes during late-night writing sessions,
上帝喝得烂醉
when God was deep in his cups,
可能透露过一些话
he may have let slip a few choice words.
但是呢
But…
我什么都不会告诉你的
I don't have to tell you anything.
你又健忘了吧
Are you forgetting?
你现在是人类了 我能把你当虫子一样捏爆
You are human now, and I could crush you like a bug.
你是可以 但你不会的
Could, but you won't.
你以为我没发现吗
You think I didn't notice?
你坏掉了 卡西迪奥
You are broken, Castiel.
你一向娘里娘气的 但这次呢
You were always a bit of a Nancy, but this?
你简直变成了大怂蛋
You have gone full wuss.
我不知道到底是怎么回事
I don't know what it was that happened,
但无论怎样
but whatever it was,
你伤痕累累 重伤
you are scarred…deep,
因为受伤和恐惧而深感无力
paralyzed by trauma, by fear.
瞧瞧你自己吧
I mean, look at you.
你连打我都做不到
You can't even hit me!
这不是恐惧
It's not fear.
蠢货 过来
Hey, idiot, andale …
这是「赶紧滚过来」的西班牙语
Spanish for "Get your ass over here."
- 你以为我这五周来一直 - 陛下
- You think I've been paying your astronomical bar tabs… - Sir?
帮你付天文数字的酒吧账单
For the past five weeks.
就为让你跟前一晚认识的小骚货一觉睡到大下午吗
so you can sleep past noon with last night's skank?
迪恩
Well, Dean?
萨姆
Sam?
这样 你去吧
You know what? Go.
干掉她
Take her out.
我来对付他们
I got them.
我就知道你会来
I knew you'd come.
抱歉 阿玛拉
I'm sorry, Amara.
为什么
For what?
为我必须要做的事
What I have to do.
你好 迪恩
Hello, dean.
我家姑娘长大了
My girl's growing up.
我早该知道要不了多久
Should have known it wouldn't be long.
小伙子们就会来打探
before the boys came sniffing around.
你到底想要跟她做什么 克劳力
What do you want with her, Crowley?
你以为你能利用她 控制她吗
What, you think you can use her, control her?
你真是白痴
You're an idiot.
我并没有想控制她
I'm not trying to control her.
我是在帮她
I'm helping her.
让她实现自己全部的潜力
to realize her fullest potential.
你知道这让我多烦恼吗
Do you know how disturbing it was.
因为我知道自己根本不舍得杀你
to realize that I couldn't bring myself to kill you?
这些年来 我有无数的机会
I've had tons of chances over the years,
有些你根本毫不知情 但是
some you don't even know about, but, still…
我还是接受了
I made my peace with it,
接受我心软的一面
embraced my softer side,
还有接受
learned to accept that.
你我之间的感情实在太复杂
there was just too much going on between you and I …
兄弟情谊
bromance.
可是你知道吗
But you know what?
我想我今天要杀了你
I think I am gonna kill you today.
我感觉有所不同了 准备好了
I feel different somehow, ready.
说什么好呢
What can I say?
父爱能改变一个人
Fatherhood changes a man.
黑暗 你都知道些什么
The Darkness … what do you know?
好吧
Okay.
我判断失误
So I misjudged.
你不是怕了 你是疯了
You're not scared. You're mad.
我明白的
And I get it.
那感觉一定很糟吧 被每个人当工具使
I mean, it must suck being everyone's tool,
被天使 被敌人 被朋友
manipulated and used by the angels,
操纵和利用
by your enemies, by your friends.
你以为假如你拿回了能量
You thought if you could get your grace back,
就能治好自己 但并没如愿
it would help fix you, but it hasn't!
黑暗
The darkness.
为什么 阿玛拉
Why, Amara?
我还以为我们达成了共识
I thought we had an understanding.
没错 你保证过要保护我的
Yeah. Your promise to protect me.
然后几小时后 我就在自己房里遭到攻击
And, then, hours later, I'm assaulted in my own room.
你看起来也并不很生气啊
Well, you don't seem terribly upset by it.
那不是重点
That's not the point.
我认为我不需要你的保护了
I've decided I don't need your protection,
更不需要你的禁锢
and I certainly don't need your captivity.
我不玩了
I'm done.
你是在尝试「不杀」政策吗
You trying out some kind of no-kill policy?
你这么愤怒 这么迷失
Who do you have to thank.
都是谁的过呢
for how angry you are, how lost?
不客气
You're welcome.
是个猎人
Oh, a hunter.
你是最该清楚的
You of all people should know.
反战主义没好果子
pacifism doesn't pay.
动手吧 卡西迪奥 杀了我吧
Go on, Castiel. End me.
不
No.
好吧 三个中有俩还活着
All right. Two out of three.
迪恩
Dean?!
Dean!
你现在该
It's time … time for you.
秒回你的王位
to blink your tired ass back to your throne.
舔舐你的伤口了
and lick your wounds.
我会饶你一命 但有个条件
I'll spare your life on one condition.
我走之后 放迪恩安全离开
Safe passage for Dean out of here after I've gone.
成交
Yes!
很好
Good.
现在…
Now…
滚出我的房间
get out of my room.
求你了 卡西迪奥
Oh, please, Castiel.
救救我
Help me.
你不说自己挺快活的吗
You said you were happy,
还自力更生呢
your "bootstraps."
我是装的
I was faking it.
我以为「能有多难呢」
I mean, I thought, "how … how hard could it be?"
你不会的
You won't.
你不能
You can't.
我撑不下去了
Can't take any more,
这种凡人生活我一天也过不下去了
not a single human day.
我是说…
I mean…
各种羞辱…根本停不下来
the indignities … they just don't stop …
赚钱…
Make…
赚钱交房租
making my rent.
不断给手机充电…
and keeping my phone charged…
还长痔疮
hemorrhoids.
你说得对 梅塔特隆
You were right, Metatron.
我受够了被人摆布利用
I am sick of having my strings pulled,
所以我不会让你操纵我
which is why I won't let you manipulate me.
给你个痛快的了断
into letting you off easy.
告诉我关于黑暗的事
Tell me about the darkness.
告诉我 我们之间到底怎么回事
Tell me, what is happening here between us?
你救我 我救你
You save me, I save you.
怎么了
What?
我被释放后第一眼看到的就是你
You were the first thing I saw when I was freed,
而且我被关了好久啊
and it had been so long.
也许就是因为这个
Maybe that's it …
你是我看到的第一个他的创造物
my first experience of his creation.
在我眼中你不由自主地成了这种代表
You can't help but represent that for me …
那美妙的胜利
the sweet triumph.
以及更加美妙的他所锻造的荒唐
and the even sweeter folly of what he's wrought.
无法抗拒
There's no fighting it.
我被迷住了
I'm fascinated.
真相…
The truth …
会让那些圣经脑残粉三观炸裂的
it'd make the Bible-Thumper's heads explode.
他们希望他们的上帝
I mean, they want their God.
弹弹手指就能搞定一切
to be a-a f-finger-snapping,
是个全能的造物主
all-powerful creator, you know…
他们想要…魔法…
And they want… magic…
波平斯阿姨那样的魔法保姆
Mary Poppins.
但是他的所作所为…
But what he did …
造物…
creation…
是需要出力的
that took work.
需要牺牲
Took sacrifice.
为了创造世界
In order to create the world,
上帝只能放弃
God had to give up.
他当时的唯一
the only thing he'd ever known.
他不得不背叛 牺牲
He had to betray and sacrifice.
他唯一的亲人
his only kin.
黑暗
The Darkness…
他妹妹
His sister.
很高兴再见到你 迪恩
It's been great seeing you again, Dean,
但我该走了
but it's time for me to go.
外面有整个世界等着我去探索
There's a whole world out there for me to explore,
我简直能尝到它的味道了
and I can practically taste it.
很快 我就将足够强大实现我来这里的目的
Soon, I'll be strong enough to do what I came here to do.
什么目的
What's that?
算笔旧账
Settle an old score …
最古老的旧账
The oldest score.
我就说吧
Told you.
听着 各位 天使妹妹满血复原
Look, guys, I'm as glad as anyone.
我和大家一样高兴 好吗
that Stella got her groove back, okay?
但你放梅塔特隆走了
But you let Metatron go?
迪恩 你要重复多少遍这个问题
Dean, how many times are you gonna repeat that question?
我要再说一次
I'm gonna say it again.
你放梅塔特隆走了
You let Metatron go!
他哪也去不了
He's not going anywhere.
如果他有动作 如果他引起了丁点的注意
If he makes a move, if he draws the slightest attention,
天使军队就会灭了他
the full force of angelkind will snuff him out.
你们两人都没看见他
Look, you … neither of you saw him.
他是个人类 而且非常可怜
He is a human, and a pitiable one at that.
他对我们不构成威胁
He's not a threat to us.
我真让他很不好过
I-I mean, I put him in traction.
二位 现在还有更重要的事
Guys, bigger fish to fry here.
阿玛拉消失了
Amara is in the wind.
是啊 上帝的妹妹
Yeah, God's freaking sister.
你说你就差一点
You said you were close.
迪恩 她是怎么逃走的
Dean, how'd she get away?
抱歉 「上帝的妹妹」
I'm sorry, what part of.
这句话你没听明白吗
"God's freaking sister" did you not understand?
她比我厉害 就这样
She overpowered me … end of story.
我们有什么计划
What's our plan here, fellas?
你说你从梅塔特隆那儿套到了一切情报 对吗
You said you got everything you could out of Metatron, right?
所以我们要去那儿找到
So, where on earth are we gonna find an answer.
如何阻止她的答案
on how to stop her?
上帝没分享过他的想法吧
I don't suppose God's decided to share any wisdom on the matter.
我去查查传说
I'll look into the lore.